export default data = [
  {
      question: "My mom puts the ______ on to keep her hands away from water when she washes the dishes",
      options: ["gloves","jacket","ring","socks"],
      correct_option: "gloves"
  },
  {
      question: "Can you ______ your feet a little off the floor? I want to see if my keys are under the sofa",
      options: ["check","kick","raise","show"],
      correct_option: "raise"
  },
  {
      question: "______ of my sisters are older than I am. I’m the youngest of the three children in my family",
      options: ["Both","Few","Most","Some"],
      correct_option: "Both"
  },
  {
      question: "The beach near our town is a very ______ place. Every summer at least one kid dies there in the water",
      options: ["dangerous","exciting","lonely","popular"],
      correct_option: "dangerous"
  },
  {
      question: "My wife enjoys going to the movies with her friends, but I like to watch TV at home by ______",
      options: ["I","me","myself","mine"],
      correct_option: "myself"
  },
  {
      question: "For the past twenty years, my father ______ in a school library. But he’ll leave the job next month",
      options: ["worked","has worked","is working","works"],
      correct_option: "has worked"
  },
  {
      question: "It’s great that we can buy train tickets over the phone without going out. It ______ us a lot of time",
      options: ["lends","prepares","saves","takes"],
      correct_option: "saves"
  },
  {
      question: "Mozart ______ his first music when he was only six years old",
      options: ["is writing","has written","will write","wrote"],
      correct_option: "wrote"
  },
  {
      question: "Jill: Have you decided ______ you will celebrate your 30th birthday? Sue: Yeah, I’m going to have a big barbecue party",
      options: ["how","where","what","when"],
      correct_option: "how"
  },
  {
      question: "Alison doesn’t like ______ what to do. She only does things she wants to do",
      options: ["told","to tell","be told","to be told"],
      correct_option: "to be told"
  },
  {
      question: "Josh has planned to make a trip to New York and ______ some of his friends there",
      options: ["visit","visits","visiting","visited"],
      correct_option: "visit"
  },
  {
      question: "Ms. Johnson has been taking phone calls since she entered the office this morning. Just when she thought she could finally leave work, ______ call came in",
      options: ["another","each","the next","the other"],
      correct_option: "another"
  },
  {
      question: "We were so sure that Jerry ______ well on the difficult job. His past experience in other work showed he was the right guy for it. So when he failed, no one believed it",
      options: ["had done","did","has done","would do"],
      correct_option: "would do"
  },
  {
      question: "For Mike, the price is ______ important thing when he shops for jeans. He cares even more about the shape and the size of the pockets",
      options: ["the more","the most","the less","the least"],
      correct_option: "the least"
  },
]
